<resources xmlns:xliff="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2">
    <string name="app_name">
        <xliff:g id="id_app_name">DilemaXXI</xliff:g>
    </string>
    <string name="genre">Genre</string>
    <string name="releases">Release Date</string>
    <string name="director">Director</string>
    <string name="like">Like</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="description">Overview</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="movie_title">Movie Title</string>
    <string name="director_name">Director Name</string>
    <string name="detail_release">Detail Release</string>
    <string name="rating">Rating</string>
    <string name="detail_description">Detail Description</string>
    <string name="detail_genre">Detail Genre</string>
    <string name="img_movie">img_movie</string>
    <string name="tv_series">TV SERIES</string>
    <string name="movie">MOVIE</string>

    <string-array name="film_name">
        <item>Spider-Man: Into the Spider Verse</item>
        <item>Avengers: Infinity War</item>
        <item>Black Panther</item>
        <item>Aquaman</item>
        <item>Deadpool 2</item>
        <item>AntMan and the Wasp</item>
        <item>Venom</item>
        <item>Ralph Breaks the Internet </item>
        <item>Mission: Impossible - Fallout</item>
        <item>High Strung Free Dance</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="series_name">
        <item>Sword Art Online: Alicization - War of Underworld</item>
        <item>Shinchou Yuusha: Kono Yuusha ga Ore Tueee Kuse ni Shinchou Sugiru</item>
        <item>Ore wo Suki nano wa Omae dake ka yo</item>
        <item>Assassins Pride</item>
        <item>Psycho-Pass 3</item>
        <item>Beastars</item>
        <item>No Guns Life</item>
        <item>Fate/Grand Order: Zettai Majuu Sensen Babylonia</item>
        <item>Hataage! Kemono Michi</item>
        <item>Bokutachi wa Benkyou ga Dekinai!</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="image_film">
        <item>@drawable/image01</item>
        <item>@drawable/image02</item>
        <item>@drawable/image03</item>
        <item>@drawable/image04</item>
        <item>@drawable/image05</item>
        <item>@drawable/image06</item>
        <item>@drawable/image07</item>
        <item>@drawable/image08</item>
        <item>@drawable/image09</item>
        <item>@drawable/image10</item>
    </array>

    <array name="image_series_film">
        <item>@drawable/series01</item>
        <item>@drawable/series02</item>
        <item>@drawable/series03</item>
        <item>@drawable/series04</item>
        <item>@drawable/series05</item>
        <item>@drawable/series06</item>
        <item>@drawable/series07</item>
        <item>@drawable/series08</item>
        <item>@drawable/series09</item>
        <item>@drawable/series10</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="film_desc">
        <item><xliff:g id="role_name">Miles Morales</xliff:g> is juggling his life between being a high school student and being a <xliff:g id="super_hero_name">spider-man</xliff:g>. When <xliff:g id="role_name">Wilson</xliff:g> "Kingpin" Fisk uses a super collider, others from across the Spider-Verse are transported to this dimension.</item>
        <item>As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all of reality. Everything the <xliff:g id="associate_hero">Avengers</xliff:g> have fought for has led up to this moment  the fate of Earth and existence itself has never been more uncertain.</item>
        <item>King <xliff:g id="Tchalla_name">TChalla</xliff:g> returns home from America to the reclusive, technologically advanced African nation of <xliff:g id="african_nation">Wakanda</xliff:g> to serve as his countrys new leader. However, <xliff:g id="role_name">TChalla</xliff:g> soon finds that he is challenged for the throne by factions within his own country as well as without. Using powers reserved to <xliff:g id="king_name">Wakandan</xliff:g> kings, <xliff:g id="role_name">TChalla</xliff:g> assumes the <xliff:g id="hero_name">Black Panther</xliff:g> mantel to join with girlfriend <xliff:g id="role_name">Nakia</xliff:g>, <xliff:g id="role_name">the queenmother</xliff:g>, his <xliff:g id="role_name">princesskid</xliff:g> sister, members of the <xliff:g id="role_name">Dora Milaje</xliff:g> and an American secret agent, to prevent <xliff:g id="african_nation">Wakanda</xliff:g> from being dragged into a world war.</item>
        <item>Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, Atlantis is now an underwater kingdom ruled by the power hungry King Orm. With a vast army at his disposal, Orm plans to conquer the remaining oceanic people and then the surface world. Standing in his way is Arthur Curry, Orms half human, half Atlantean brother and true heir to the throne.</item>
        <item>Wisecracking mercenary <xliff:g id="super_hero_name">Deadpool</xliff:g> battles the evil and powerful Cable and other bad guys to save a boys life.</item>
        <item>Just when his time under house arrest is about to end, Scott Lang once again puts his freedom at risk to help <xliff:g id="role_name">Hope van Dyne</xliff:g> and <xliff:g id="role_name">Dr. Hank Pym</xliff:g> dive into the quantum realm and try to accomplish, against time and any chance of success, a very dangerous rescue mission.</item>
        <item>Investigative journalist <xliff:g id="role_name">Eddie Brock</xliff:g> attempts a comeback following a scandal, but accidentally becomes the host of Venom, a violent, super powerful alien symbiote. Soon, he must rely on his newfound powers to protect the world from a shadowy organization looking for a symbiote of their own.</item>
        <item>Video game bad guy <xliff:g id="role_name">Ralph</xliff:g> and fellow misfit <xliff:g id="role_name">Vanellope von Schweetz</xliff:g> must risk it all by traveling to the World Wide Web in search of a replacement part to save <xliff:g id="role_name">Vanellopes</xliff:g> video game, <xliff:g id="film_name">Sugar Rush</xliff:g>. In way over their heads, <xliff:g id="role_name">Ralph</xliff:g> and <xliff:g id="role_name">Vanellope</xliff:g> rely on the citizens of the internet  the <xliff:g id="role_name">netizens</xliff:g>  to help navigate their way, including an entrepreneur named <xliff:g id="role_name">Yesss</xliff:g>, who is the head algorithm and the heart and soul of trend making site <xliff:g id="site_name">BuzzzTube</xliff:g>.</item>
        <item>When an IMF mission ends badly, the world is faced with dire consequences. As <xliff:g id="role_name">Ethan Hunt</xliff:g> takes it upon himself to fulfill his original briefing, the CIA begin to question his loyalty and his motives. The IMF team find themselves in a race against time, hunted by assassins while trying to prevent a global catastrophe.</item>
        <item><xliff:g id="role_name">Zander Raines</xliff:g>, a dazzling and tempestuous young choreographer, gives the break of a lifetime to two hopeful artists when he casts a stunning contemporary dancer, Barlow, and innovative pianist, Charlie, in <xliff:g id="city">New York’s</xliff:g> most anticipated new Broadway show: Free Dance. But the move throws off the show’s delicate creative balance when <xliff:g id="role_name">Charlie falls</xliff:g> hard for Barlow while <xliff:g id="role_name">Zander</xliff:g> embraces her as his muse.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="film_series_desc">
        <item>Despite the defeat of <xliff:g id="role_name">Quinella</xliff:g>—the pontifex of the Axiom Church—things have not seemed to calm down yet. Upon contacting the real world, <xliff:g id="role_name">Kazuto "Kirito" Kirigaya</xliff:g> finds out that the Ocean Turtle—a mega-float controlled by Rat was raided. Due to a sudden short-circuit caused by the raiders, <xliff:g id="role_name">Kirito\'s</xliff:g> fluct light is damaged, leaving him comatose. Feeling insecure about the people at the Axiom Church, <xliff:g id="role_name">Alice brings</xliff:g> the unconscious <xliff:g id="role_name">Kirito</xliff:g> back to their hometown—<xliff:g id="village_name">Rulid</xliff:g> Village, disregarding her banishment due to an unabsolved crime. Now, <xliff:g id="role_name">Alice</xliff:g> is living an ordinary and peaceful life close by the village, wishing for <xliff:g id="role_name">Kirito</xliff:g> to wake up.However, tragedy strikes when <xliff:g id="role_name">Alice</xliff:g> notices that the Dark Territory has already started to invade the Human Empire. Reassuming her previous alias, <xliff:g id="role_name">Alice Synthesis Thirty</xliff:g>, she promises to defeat the Dark Territory in order to defend the world that <xliff:g id="role_name">Kirito</xliff:g> and <xliff:g id="role_name">Eugeo</xliff:g> worked so hard to protect.</item>
        <item>There is a popular saying: "you can never be too careful." It is very important to prepare for every situation you may face, even if it seems like an unnecessary waste of time. Also, in games like RPGs, it is good to exceed the level of your enemies to achieve total victory.These words describe <xliff:g id="role_name">Seiya Ryuuguuin</xliff:g> a little too perfectly. After being summoned by the goddess Ristarte to save the world of Gaeabrande from destruction, the hero prepares himself for his noble journey. While this might be normal, he spends a very long time training himself, despite having overpowered stats. He fights weak enemies using his strongest skills and buys excessive amounts of supplies and potions—all to stay safe.While his attitude may be a bit annoying, it might just be the saving grace of <xliff:g id="role_name">Gaeabrande</xliff:g>, especially considering that it is a world where the forces of evil dominate each and every expectation.</item>
        <item><xliff:g id="role_name">Amatsuyu "Jouro"</xliff:g> Kisaragi is a completely average second-year high school student who has two dates over one weekend⁠—with the student council president <xliff:g id="role_name">Sakura</xliff:g> "Cosmos" <xliff:g id="role_name">Akino</xliff:g> on Saturday, then with his childhood friend <xliff:g id="role_name">Aoi "Himawari" Hinata</xliff:g> on Sunday. Sadly for <xliff:g id="role_name">Jouro</xliff:g>, both girls proclaim their love for his best friend Taiyou "Sun-chan" Ooga, the ace of the baseball team. Accepting each of their requests for advice and guidance, he is now responsible for helping the two girls win the heart of the same guy.</item>
        <item>On the brink of extinction, mankind has downsized and now solely resides in the city-state of <xliff:g id="city_state">Flandore</xliff:g>, living in cities encased by glass domes. Beyond the domes exist vicious lycanthropes who thrive in the darkness; among the citizens inside, a clear distinction between the nobility and commoners is in place. The blood of nobles enables them to utilize mana, granting them abilities that exceed human limits and greatly assist them in defeating <xliff:g id="role_name">lycanthropes</xliff:g>.</item>
        <item>Thanks to the Sibyl System, the mental states of society can now be measured on a numerical scale. Using these "crime coefficients," a culprit can be apprehended before they ever commit a crime. But is it a perfect system? For Inspectors <xliff:g id="role_name">Kei Mikhail Ignatov</xliff:g> and <xliff:g id="role_name">Arata Shindou</xliff:g>, that remains to be seen, as their career with the Public Safety Bureau\'s Crime Investigation Department has only just begun.<xliff:g id="role_name">Shindou</xliff:g> and <xliff:g id="role_name">Ignatov</xliff:g> are assigned to investigate the crash of a ship carrying immigrants, but they begin to suspect that it was no mere accident. Meanwhile, a mysterious group called <xliff:g id="role_name">Bifrost</xliff:g> is observing them from the shadows, but they aren\'t the only ones who have taken an interest in the two new Inspectors.</item>
        <item>In a civilized society of anthropomorphic animals, an uneasy tension exists between carnivores and herbivores. At <xliff:g id="academy_name">Cherryton Academy</xliff:g>, this mutual distrust peaks after a predation incident results in the death of Tem, an alpaca in the school\'s drama club. Tem\'s friend <xliff:g id="role_name">Legoshi</xliff:g>, a grey wolf in the stage crew, has been an object of fear and suspicion for his whole life. In the immediate aftermath of the tragedy, he continues to lay low and hide his menacing traits, much to the disapproval of Louis, a red deer and the domineering star actor of the drama club.</item>
        <item>The technology to create powerful cyborg soldiers has been released for public use by the <xliff:g id="corporation_name">Berühren</xliff:g> Corporation. Those outfitted with robotic parts are known as the Extended. <xliff:g id="role_name">Juuzou Inui</xliff:g>, one such Extended, was created as a soldier and has no memories of his former life. But now, after the war, he runs a business that takes care of Extended-related incidents around the city. </item>
        <item>A.D. 2016, the foundations of humanity have been incinerated by the Mage King Solomon. Chaldea, a secret mages organization with the mission to preserve humanity\'s future, foresaw mankind\'s extinction in 2015. Thus commenced the operation to repair the Singularities in history caused by Holy Grails dispersed across time and space—Operation Grand Order. </item>
        <item>Professional wrestler Genzou Shibata sports the body of a mountain, but beneath his hulking appearance is a man with an extreme affection for animals. Facing off his opponents in the ring as the legendary "Animal Mask," Genzou wins the hearts of crowds everywhere with his iconic tiger persona.</item>
        <item>Under <xliff:g id="role_name">Nariyuki Yuiga\'s</xliff:g> devoted tutelage, his classmates <xliff:g id="role_name">Rizu Ogata</xliff:g>, <xliff:g id="role_name">Fumino Furuhashi</xliff:g>, and <xliff:g id="role_name">Uruka Takemoto</xliff:g> are finally pulling average test scores on their worst subjects. But time is ticking, and there is still a long way to go before the three geniuses of <xliff:g id="academy_name">Ichinose Academy</xliff:g> are ready for their upcoming university exams. Meanwhile, the girls still struggle to balance the pursuit of their dreams with their growing affections for their unsuspecting tutor.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Genre">
        <item>ACTION|ADVENTURE|ANIMATION|SCIFI|COMEDY</item>
        <item>ADVENTURE|ACTION|SCIFI</item>
        <item>ACTION|ADVENTURE|FANTASY|SCIFI</item>
        <item>ACTION|ADVENTURE|FANTASY</item>
        <item>ACTION|COMEDY|ADVENTURE</item>
        <item>ACTION|ADVENTURE|SCIFI|COMEDY</item>
        <item>SCIFI|ACTION</item>
        <item>FAMILY|ANIMATION|COMEDY|ADVENTURE</item>
        <item>ACTION|ADVENTURE</item>
        <item>ROMANCE|FAMILY</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="genre_series">
        <item>Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Game, Romance</item>
        <item>Action, Adventure, Comedy, Fantasy</item>
        <item>Comedy, Romance, School</item>
        <item>Fantasy</item>
        <item>Action, Police, Psychological, Sci-Fi</item>
        <item>Drama, Psychological, Shounen, Slice of Life</item>
        <item>Action, Sci-Fi, Drama, Seinen</item>
        <item>Action, Fantasy, Magic, Supernatural</item>
        <item>Comedy, Fantasy, Shounen</item>
        <item>Comedy, Harem, Romance, School, Shounen</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Rating">
        <item>8.4</item>
        <item>8.3</item>
        <item>7.4</item>
        <item>6.8</item>
        <item>7.5</item>
        <item>7.0</item>
        <item>6.6</item>
        <item>7.2</item>
        <item>7.3</item>
        <item>7.2</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="rating_series">
        <item>7.9</item>
        <item>7.5</item>
        <item>7.8</item>
        <item>6.5</item>
        <item>7.9</item>
        <item>8.2</item>
        <item>7.1</item>
        <item>7.9</item>
        <item>7.0</item>
        <item>7.6</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="release">
        <item>December 6, 2018</item>
        <item>April 25, 2018</item>
        <item>February 13, 2018</item>
        <item>December 7, 2018</item>
        <item>May 10, 2018</item>
        <item>July 4, 2018</item>
        <item>September 28, 2018</item>
        <item>November 20, 2018</item>
        <item>July 13, 2018</item>
        <item>September 13, 2018</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="release_series">
        <item>Oct 13, 2019 to ?</item>
        <item>Oct 2, 2019 to Dec 25, 2019</item>
        <item>Oct 3, 2019 to ?</item>
        <item>Oct 10, 2019 to ?</item>
        <item>Oct 25, 2019 to ?</item>
        <item>Oct 10, 2019 to ?</item>
        <item>Oct 11, 2019 to ?</item>
        <item>Oct 5, 2019 to Mar, 2020</item>
        <item>Oct 2, 2019 to Dec 18, 2019</item>
        <item>Oct 6, 2019 to ?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="directors">
        <item>Bob Persichetti, Peter Ramsey </item>
        <item>Joe Russo</item>
        <item>Ryan Coogler</item>
        <item>James Wan</item>
        <item>David Leitch</item>
        <item>Peyton Reed</item>
        <item>Ruben Fleischer</item>
        <item>Phil Johnston</item>
        <item>Christopher McQuarrie</item>
        <item>Michael Damian</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="studio">
        <item>A-1 Pictures</item>
        <item>White Fox</item>
        <item>Connect</item>
        <item>EMT Squared</item>
        <item>Production I.G</item>
        <item>Orange</item>
        <item>Madhouse</item>
        <item>CloverWorks</item>
        <item>ENGI</item>
        <item>Silver, Arvo Animation</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="series_title">Series Title</string>
    <string name="trailer">Trailer</string>
    <string name="image_favorite">Image Favorite</string>
    <string name="image_rating">Image Rating</string>
    <string name="studio_name">Studio Name</string>
    <string name="studio">Studio</string>
    <string name="image_movie">Image Movie</string>
    <string name="image_tv_series">Image Tv Series</string>
    <string name="image_actor">Image Actor</string>
    <string name="actor">Actor</string>
    <string name="change_language_settings">Change Language Settings</string>
    <string name="background">Background</string>


</resources>
